(Leonard:)I deliberately tried to sabotage
Stuart's date with Penny.
(Raj:)Of course you feel terrible. You completely
screwed up your karma, dude.
(Sheldon:)You don't really believe in that superstition,
do you?
(Raj:)It's not superstition,
it's practically Newtonian.
(Raj:)For every action,
there's an equal and opposite reaction.
(Raj:)Leonard pretends to be a friend,
and acts like a two-faced bitch.
(Raj:)Therefore, he is reborn as a banana slug.
(Raj:)It's actually a very elegant system.
You know, what goes around comes around.
(Howard:)Speaking of what goes around
comes around...
(Raj:)Okay, look.
(Raj:)Instead of trying to reinforce
this structure here...
...what if we ran another line,
bypassed it entirely?
(Sheldon:)Won't work.
The diameter of the tubing is insufficient.
(Raj:)What if we reposition
the collection tank?
(Sheldon:)It won't work. No way to mount it.
(Howard:)Here's an idea.
What if I change my name...
(Howard:)...and go live with my cousin
and her husband, Avi, in Israel?
(Sheldon:)That could work.